And let me tell you the condition of the stock market, on the
first day of the trading week, there was a great bullish mood in the market, the
Nifty bank reached a
new record of 44483, while the
Sensex finally rose by 344 songs to
close at the level of 62846, the Nifty rose by about 100 songs and closed
near 18600 and
what was the specialty of the market, let us understand from our colleague
Ashish Chaturvedi,
see, the
start of the Indian markets was very spectacular
because if you look at it, the
dodging that was there regarding the matter has been
resolved to some extent, due to this we saw that
SGX Nifty today with a start of 120-150 points at
6:30 in the morning
was indicating that the Indian market will be bullish and
if you look at it as soon as it opens, the Nifty bank has
broken its previous, that is, the time
high breakout, which was made on 14 December 2022,
if you look from there, then a
new record has been made today, Nifty bank is here
for a good third closing,
if you look from today also, then a very good level  But
if you talk about Nifty, then it was
closing around ₹590, around ₹18592. Here you have also seen on Nifty the
stock especially Fox Mirage.
If you see here, after the good results
of positive reports, there was a good rise of 4%.
Yesterday
you saw surprising moves of 2% in India
and another name in the metal pack is
Tata Steel, where you saw the gains of two days ago,
but after the weakness, there is an on-
stock where you saw a sharp decline. If we
talk about uninsted, then
look at ICC Lombard, there is news whether
ICC Bank can increase its stake here.
After this, during which, up to 11-12%
gains were seen, but
in the end, if you see, with a gain of 8%,
which are the highlights? Badal
Engineer India's continuous teaser, GMR
Airports' result was very weak. City Union
Bank also had a similar result, the result was very
weak, a 10% decline was seen here.
got it and Balkrishna Industries also
fell by 8% due to similar Tarak but
how is Nucleus Software, it
can gain 20% on Friday as well, this time
also a rise of 20% was seen, there is a good break out in Green Lab
potato contract Mahindra Lifes,
you have seen a rise of 8% here but Grapes Cotton
Alcohol Engineering G Power and Kim Kaun are
some of the stocks especially in which you will see a fall
[Music]